Count Kruteo, you said?
Yes. The title has gone to his eldest son.
Clonkane.
My research indicates the young count possesses intense loyalty for the Emperor.
Those who have not submitted and joined us are all loyal to Verse.
If we could get him to join us, it might be possible to have them all change sides at once.
Indeed.
The question, of course, is whether he can be trusted with our vision.
Deucalion, prepare to lift off. Engines ahead, dead slow.
Engines ahead, dead slow.
Prepare ship to leave atmosphere. Course heading, satellite belt.
Our staging area is Parnasso Space.
Please keep crack.
Please, we 아니면 call
extremist advisors at the affiliationpora
Let's do this.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
I love you, sir.
There's nothing in the sky
Let's play a game
We've lost our eyes
We've lost our words
So, ah, it's more fun
It's not
I'm falling, it's not
形だけのシステムと
畳だけの間違いも
共に無恥じらいを
想像大キャリオン
いじるタイム
迎えられる通り
ゼロが眠りかけた
たけがいない
人と戦士
かわにあるぞろたち
また同じかてに
ほがいて
ご視聴ありがとうございました
mogだし
見えると
ご視聴された
目 Report
そして
に tear
耳 Georgia
のために
を
openings
へ тоже
will split our forces for this operation.
Bretton Company and the Deucalion,
at 2200 hours Earth Standard Time,
you will initiate your attack against the Landing Castle.
Once we confirm that a portion of Moon Base forces
are en route to defend the Landing Castle,
Traichner Company will deploy to the field
of large boulders surrounding the fortress.
They will use these boulders as cover
while they approach the enemy base and strike.
Headquarters has given this action
to the designation Operation Luna Gate.
I beg your forgiveness, m'lady,
if I had just not been so careless.
Not at all.
Blame, if there is any, must rest with me.
Everything, this entire situation, is all my fault.
You mustn't say such things, m'lady.
You are right.
Had you remained asleep,
everything would have gone smoothly,
with no worry or complication.
I would not have wept all those tears.
And his soul would not have become so corrupted.
I can tell that you care about slain.
I can see that in you.
And what about you?
What do you see in yourself?
Huh?
Who do you care for?
My heart belongs to the world of Verse,
to those dwelling there who require my help and my guidance.
That is what I was taught, and how I live.
I feel sorry for you.
Along with Breton Company, we've been tasked with attacking the Landing Castle.
This operation is on two fronts, and that part is our responsibility.
It is the mission headquarters has assigned to the Ducalion.
An operation on two fronts?
Basically, we're here to get the enemy to divide up his forces, by dangling the ship as bait once again.
However, I do not intend to needlessly endanger this ship or her crew.
So keep your heads down, and don't throw your lives away.
I want you all doing your best until we return to Earth.
Dismissed.
All right, all hands to your assigned stations.
Captain.
I had a feeling you might want a word.
I have something to discuss with you, too.
Thank you for your patience.
I understand that you have come all this way to offer your condolences for my father, Count Sosbaum.
We are a very long way from verse, after all.
That, Count Troyard, and the fact that congratulations on your title are long overdue.
And I must apologize for failing to congratulate you on your succession to the rank of Count Cruteo.
I am still unaccustomed to that title.
Call me Clankane, please.
Yes, whatever you prefer, then.
Now, Princess Asalem.
She had been so looking forward to seeing you again, after such a long time.
I heard that she had not been feeling well.
One really cannot be too careful when it comes to health.
I confess, I am most indebted to your late father.
He was not too rough on you, then.
I must admit, he was a man who could be stern to a fault.
Well, he taught me a great many valuable lessons.
I would not be who I am today, had it not been for your father.
I did see the Tharsis.
I am pleased, Count Troyard, that it seems to have been of use to you.
I heard while we were still underway,
something about Earthspace and your plans to found a new kingdom?
That is correct.
It is the wish of Princess Asalem.
Is it also the wish of his majesty?
It is my understanding he is not well.
Our top medical staff are caring for him with the very latest equipment.
So there is no cause for concern.
That is good news, indeed.
And when Princess Asalem's wish does come true,
I am certain that his majesty will be delighted.
Yes, one would certainly hope so.
If you were to lend us your support, Lord Cloncain,
well, it would be most reassuring.
I look forward to it.
And to seeing how this new kingdom will affect the future of Verse.
Analysis of the rock clusters with unnatural behavior suggests objects of different mass behind them.
Camouflage.
And Stygia Squadron?
Ready for immediate launch.
Escort Lord Cloncain to a safe location.
At this speed, we'll be in effective firing range in seven minutes.
We'll draw the battle line back with us after we engage them,
separating the enemy force from the moon base.
All hands to battle stations.
All launch teams, prepare to initiate catapult sequence.
Flywheel connected.
Catapult arm rotation initiated.
Open hatches for launch.
Claddesdale platoon, move to position.
Roger.
Claddesdale leader to all units.
Let's move out.
Anchors engaged.
Arm rotation nominal and steady.
Arm accelerating.
Go for launch 20 seconds.
Claddesdale leader, you are now clear for launch.
Roger that.
You are go for launch.
Let's do this.
Whoa!
Mustang platoon, prepare yourselves for launch.
Brenton Company and Deucalion have launched.
I say again, they have launched.
Roger that.
Come on, guys, we're up.
Commence attack!
Sir, multiple hostile pings detected toward Libra.
Cataphract!
Intercept them.
It started.
Yeah.
Their defenses.
They look pretty tough, all right.
Foregone conclusion that this was going to be tough.
And the reason that we're pushing ahead with this operation and the reason that we're pushing
ahead with this operation, regardless of that, is because headquarters had another mission
in mind, one the captain and I both suspected, to have an assault team sneak in under cover
of all the other battle activity.
For sabotage or something?
They wouldn't need a cover operation for that.
Their objective must be assassinating princess of Salem.
No.
They wouldn't need a cover operation for that.
Their objective must be...
Assassinating princess of Salem.
Demokratia of Alan.
Inspired julien,oscope of himself.
Hiren.
Bastard!
T disturb!
Fire!
Who's next?
90 seconds to closest approach.
Roger. Then let's stick to the plan.
Inko.
I've been planning on doing this alone.
It's going to get dangerous from here on out, so...
Oh, come on! You're not giving me that again.
The captain assigned me to provide support on this mission because of all that I've accomplished in combat.
The fact is, we have all been fighting alongside each other.
I'm sorry, Inko.
All right, let's get going.
This is close enough. I'll make the drop from here.
No, that's dangerous. We're still too high.
Enemy units!
Drop me, Inko. You can't return fire like this.
It's okay. The gravity field's a mess. At this range, I can dodge.
Inko!
A little more. Just hold on!
Good timing, Yuki.
Don't worry. I've got this.
Thanks again, Yuki.
Inko, it's safe to drop me now.
Roger.
You be careful.
This is where we split up.
Each team will be searching along their assigned route.
As soon as you spot the target, carry out the mission immediately. No delay.
Now move out.
It's an ambush!
Now we have them right where we want them.
Quite likely, the enemy has penetrated other zones as well, my lord. I will send troops to sea.
The princesses? They are secured, my lord.
My lord, Count Royard. Your servant Baro Cruz is here to provide assistance.
It's good that you came. I thank you. I will send Harklight to your location.
I wish you would tell us what's going on.
All right. I can hold them up here while the rest of you go and locate the target.
Importing base security feeds. Generating 3D map.
Using you too much, huh?
I'm all right. Position confirmed for infiltration team.
If I trace their path of advance, I'll find Salem.
We can do this. The enemy is as good as dead.
High-tension monomolecular wire wrapped around a superconducting electromagnetic spool.
There is nothing that cannot be cut by this blade.
See to any vermin left in the area.
Sir Harklight, consider it done.
Target located!
Get back, your highness!
Careful!
Run, highness! Get those doors up!
My lord slain! We have lost contact with her highness's escorts.
What's that? Where are they?
Headed for the landing port. But the enemy is going there too.
I'm sending more personnel immediately...
On my way!
Why would you be willing to assist me?
I do not need to find a reason to save someone's life.
Such arrogance...
What's that?
The suffering felt by those you save has never occurred to you.
Milady Lemrina!
Please leave me. It is my wish to remain here.
We must escape from here now!
But where are we running to?
Who are we escaping?
I know we can find a place!
There is nowhere for me to go.
This place is my only shelter.
Hm.
Now, go!
Where am I?
All right.
Let's do one more search.
I know Salem.
Must be nearby.
I didn't expect you here.
Inaho Kaisuka.
I should have known.
Slain Troyard.
Calculate firing point from the bullet path.
Thermograph.
Steam pipes.
Where is Salem now?
Where is Princess Asalem?
Don't involve her in this.
Don't you see? She was always a necessary part of the goal.
Nothing more than that.
Then you're just going to exploit her?
And if that's what I do, is it a problem?
You were always my enemy from the first time we met.
If you were merely an enemy, I wouldn't have to hate you now!
Over there!
Get him!
Let's go now!
Delritso!
Delritso! Are you injured?
Are you alright, m'lady?
Behind me, m'lady!
Salem...
I'm so glad that you're alright.
Inahu!
Salem, I am so glad that you're alright.
M'lady, wait!
Inahu, please!
Are you alright?
Oh, Inahu!
Princess Asalem vs. Eleusia. Identity confirmed.
Inahu?
Thought processes offline. Backup program initiate.
What's wrong with you?
Inahu!
Now taking over control.
Awareness, speech, and thought process being managed temporarily.
Who are you, then?
Even though aware that Princess Asalem is in fact a separate discreet individual, she is identified as part of himself.
A part of himself?
Maximum priority was placed on her safety.
Inahu Kaisuka's actions were to protect her.
He came here... to rescue me?
Providing information in conformity with that core principle.
Use communications line inside F3 gate airlock to contact Inko Amifumi.
The crew of the Deucalion? Do you mean they're here as well?
We need to hurry, m'lady. I know exactly where that airlock is.
But we... we can't leave Inahu here.
There is no need for concern. In 420 seconds, help will be arriving here.
It's even more important that we hurry now. We don't know if that help is on our side or not.
Please tell him that I said...
I said...
We need to hurry now. We don't know if that help is on our side or not.
Please tell him that I said...
Thank you from the bottom of my heart.
Command confirmed.
And also...
I...
Also identify you...
As a greatly important part of myself.
We have to go.
No, wait.
I have just...
One more favor to ask.
It's this one.
Just wait, m'lady. I'll get this transmission made.
Princess of Salem.
Now you die.
Princess of Salem. Are you hurt, your highness?
I know you.
Cloncain.
I am quite honored that you remembered me.
From my father's commendation ceremony.
Thanks for turning, psychosis and
The sound of the wind is still far away
But I can't be afraid of flying
Even if it's not the end
Ahh!
Why is it schwierigr
About of a surprise
Just keep floating
That's why we dream
I won't miss you.
If you want me, change it sobie...
You